> MTV
♪ MTV ♪
(昆虫鸣叫)
[insects chirping]
[对着电话晃来晃去]嗨，现在几点了？
[Teeter over phone] Hey, what time is it there?
[Colby]比德州早一个小时。
[Colby] Hour earlier than it is in Texas.
[提特]这不是很奇怪吗
[Teeter] Ain't it strange how it's like
不同的时间在两个地方，
different times in two places,
但我们同时在说话吗？
but we're talking at the same time?
我的声音要一个小时才能传到你耳朵里。
Hell, it should take my voice an hour to get to you.
我要让你好好想想
I'm gonna let you think that one through
别告诉任何人你说过这话。
and never tell anyone you said it.
我就是这么爱你。
That's how much I love you.
♪ gentle music ♪
♪
-你要多少钱？-我的意思是
- How much you what? - I-I mean,
作为一个人，一个朋友。
as a person, as a friend.
不要做过多解读。
Don't read too much into it.
去你妈的。你爱我，你说过了。
Oh, fuck you. You love me and you said it.
我不敢…看。
I-I'm not... Look.
我再喝两杯咖啡就能跟你谈了。
I'm two coffees away from having this conversation.
(嘲笑)
[scoffs]
嘿，你知道怎么回事吗？瑞安什么都不会告诉我们的。
Hey, you know what's going on? Ryan won't tell us nothing.
(叹息)
[sighs]
我没资格说这个。
It's not really my place to say.
但我要说的是，如果你对未来有什么大计划，
But I'll say this: if you have any big plans for the future,
我会开始研究它们。
I'd start working on them.
我有个大计划。
I got big plans.
(沃克)摇摇欲坠。
[Walker] Teeter.
[提特]我得走了。
[Teeter] I got to go.
我也爱你。
I love you, too.
[笑]
[chuckles]
-[敲打]-[叹气]
- [tapping] - [sighs]
你要怎么做？
What are you gonna do?
做什么？
Do about what?
牧场。
The ranch.
（叹气）我不知道。
[sighs] I don't know.
[乡村音乐在立体声播放]
[country music playing on stereo]
你要留下来吗？
Are you gonna stay on?
如果是凯西和里普在管的话，没错。
If Kayce's running it and Rip's running it, yeah.
某个有钱人买了它
Some rich dude buys it
就为了扮演牛仔？
just to play cowboy?
嗯，很多衣服
Eh, plenty of outfits
还在用老办法打牛。
still punching cows the old-fashioned way.
我想我得去找一个。
I guess I go find one of them.
还有其他服装吗？
What other outfits?
哦，怀俄明的阳光，
Oh, there's the Sunlight in Wyoming,
N Bar, Coffee, Q Creek。
the N Bar, the Coffee, the Q Creek.
然后是内布拉斯加州的海索恩。
Then there's the Haythorn in Nebraska.
亚利桑那州和新墨西哥州有很多大公司。
There's a bunch of big outfits in Arizona and New Mexico.
然后德州有那么多农场，
Then there's all those ranches in Texas,
但我不是为那种高温而生的。
but I ain't built for that heat.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
想要离开我们了吗？
Thinking about quitting us already?
如果农场卖了。
Well, if the ranch gets sold.
没关系。某个亿万富翁会买下它的
It don't matter. Some billionaire will buy it
一年来两次，别来烦我们。
and visit twice a year and leave us alone.
没有什么会改变。
Nothing'll change.
-反正对我们来说不是。-[劳埃德]是吗？
- Not for us, anyways. - [Lloyd] Yeah?
劳埃德，去把账簿拿来，好吗？
Lloyd, go get the ledger, will you?
(轻声咕哝声)
[grunts softly]
那些还在河底的小母牛？
Those heifers still on the river bottom?
是的，和公牛一起。这是奶牛。
Yeah, with the bulls. Here's the cows.
他们会出价45吗？
Will they bid on them at 45?
-是的。-[椅子刮伤]
- Yeah. - [chair scrapes]
去把公牛牵来，把小母牛牵来。
Go ahead and pull the bulls and bring the heifers in.
你要检查一下刹车吗，老大？
You want to brake-check 'em, boss?
不，我想卖掉它们，还有公牛。
No, I want to sell 'em. The bulls, too.
有两年前的饮料吗？
Any of them two-year-old dinks?
-里面有几个不法之徒。——是吗?伊桑?
- There's a few outlaws in there. - Yeah? Ethan?
有三四个很坏的人
Three or four that are pretty bad-minded
剩下的会来的。
and the rest will come around.
是吗?你现在有多少人在工作？
Yeah? How many you working right now?
——总?——嗯。
- Total? - Mm-hmm.
一直在调查德州克鲁兹的小马队。这是十。
Been working all the Texas Cruz colts. That's ten.
——好的。-问题儿童还有5岁
- Okay. - Problem child's another five,
然后是2，所以是17。
and then my two, so 17.
——好的。你俩怎么样了？-他们很好。
- Okay. How's your two? - They're nice.
好吧，我要你拉住他们，
All right, I want you to hold them back,
把其余的送到比林斯去。
send the rest to Billings.
我们要把它们放到拍卖会上。
We're gonna put 'em in the auction.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
我有一件不能参加拍卖的。
I got one that can't go in the auction.
婊子需要放下。
Sumbitch needs to put down.
劳埃德，想想办法。他捐款。
Lloyd, just figure it out. Donate him.
给谁，他妈的马戏团吗？他是个食人魔。
To who, the fucking circus? He's a man-eater.
好吧，我来处理。卡特?
All right, I'll take care of it. Carter?
去给三岁的孩子装鞍吧。
Go start saddling three-year-olds for everybody.
-包括我。[清喉咙]-[卡特]嗯，是的，先生。
- Me included. [clears throat] - [Carter] Uh, yes, sir.
你关心的是哪些？
You care which ones?
没关系。他们都需要骑马。
It don't matter. They all need rode.
[门开，门关]
[door opens, closes]
我要把德州的一切都签了合同。
I'm gonna put a contract on everything in Texas.
这些都被卖掉了。
It all gets sold.
一切吗?
Everything?
-整个兽群。-那我们只有
- The whole damn herd. - Then all we've got's
89号路下边的牧场有什么。
what's in the lower pasture along 89.
该死，那不是500双。
And hell, that ain't 500 pairs.
6岁以上的骟马也会被卖掉。
Any gelding that's over six years old gets sold, too.
遍历你的字符串。
So go through your string.
我们下星期要在这里搞一次特卖
We're gonna have a dispersal sale here next week
如果我们能及时振作起来。
if we can get our shit together in time.
我们去工作吧。
Let's go to work.
♪
-嘿，老板。-是的。
- [Lloyd] Hey, boss. - Yeah.
我们破产了？
We out of business?
我是想挽救公司，劳埃德。
Trying to save the business, Lloyd.
山姆大叔想要他的一磅肉。
Uncle Sam wants his pound of flesh.
我们也不想把土地给他。
And we don't want to give it to him in land.
♬拉里·弗利特的《公路之脚》
♪ "Highway Feet" by Larry Fleet ♪
♪
雷纳，她不是。
Rainer, she ain't.
(模糊聊天)
[indistinct chatter]
关.注.公.众.号.单.调.资.源.获.取.更.多.资.源.实.时.同.步.更.新
>生活在高速公路上♬
♪ Living on the highway ♪
♬让我们保持苗条和吝啬…♪我> < /
♪ Kept us lean and mean... ♪
(低声说)
[mutters]
♪ Like a fine mo-chine ♪
♪ Have to see an old tour T-shirt ♪
♬只是想知道我们都去过哪里…♪我> < /
♪ Just to find out where we've been... ♪
嘿。嘘。
Hey. Shh.
♬在我们的高速公路上，那时♬
♪ On our highway feet back then ♪
♬上帝知道这个老旅行乐队的
♪ Lord knows this ol' traveling band's ♪
♬被困了很长一段时间，躺在这里…♪我> < /
♪ Been hemmed up quite a while, laying around here... ♪
特拉维斯吉米。
[Travis] Jimmy.
你他妈在干什么？
What in the fuck are you doing?
-吉米，住手。让马停下来。-我不知道
- Jimmy, stop. Stop the horse. - I don't know
-他怎么了？他。-我知道怎么了
- what's wrong with him. He-- - Well, I know what's wrong
和他在一起。你把他弄到鳄鱼鼻子里了。
with him. You got him in a fucking gator snaffle.
-他做了什么？-你他妈看到了吗
- What'd he do? - Do you see the fucking bit
他在这匹马的嘴里？
he's got in this horse's mouth?
-（笑）看。-[男人笑]他想要
- [laughs] Look. - [man chuckles] He wants
-坐过山车。-（笑）是的。
- to ride the roller coaster. - [laughs] Yes.
-鳄鱼鼻吸是什么？呃，这是最后一站了
- What's a gator snaffle? - [Travis] Uh, it's the last stop
在大甩卖之前，伙计。
before the sale barn, man.
那是给怪物的。
That bit's for monsters.
为什么他们叫它鳄鱼鼻吸？
Why do they call it a gator snaffle?
因为你可以骑鳄鱼
Because you can ride an alligator
-和那个讨厌的混蛋。——丹妮卡
- with that nasty fucker. - [Travis] Danica,
你能把那个凯莉·凯莉给我拿来吗
can you go grab me that Kerry Kelly
在这白痴被杀之前偷吃狗骨头？
dog bone snaffle before this idiot gets killed?
你是怎么做的？你只是在早上醒来吗
What do you do? Do you just wake up in the morning
你就试着想办法
and you just try to think of ways
被人从马上摔下来吗？
to get fucking bucked off a horse?
我知道你很蠢。
Look, I know you're dumb.
我们，我们都知道你…你知道你很笨，
We-we, we all know you're... You know you're dumb,
但我没想到你有那么笨。
but I didn't think you were that fucking dumb.
我觉得你没那么蠢。
And I don't think you are that dumb.
你知道我怎么想吗？我想你坐在这里
You know what I think? I think you're sitting here
想念那个黑发小女孩
missing that little brunette
你给我把你的屁股打趴下，好吗？
and you're gonna get your ass bucked off, all right?
是你想当驯马师的，伙计。
You're the one who wanted to be a horse trainer, buddy.
好吧?你想回去找小母牛，随你便。
All right? You want to go back and prowl heifers, be my guest.
-[手机震动]-[清喉咙]对不起。
- [phone vibrating] - [clears throat] I'm sorry.
该死的。我是说，你看到我要处理的事了吗？
Goddamn. I mean, do you see the shit I have to deal with?
[笑]
[chuckles]
(叹息)
[sighs]
伙计，这个吉米真是个头昏眼花的混蛋。他妈的为什么？
Man, this Jimmy is one dizzy son of a bitch. Why the fuck
-是你们派他来的吗？——[瑞普笑]
- did y'all send him here? - [Rip chuckles]
是啊，这也是他的魅力所在。
Yeah, well, that's part of his charm.
（笑）是啊，我看不出有什么魅力。
[chuckles] Yeah, I don't see a lot of charm in it.
怎么了，兄弟？
What's going on, brother?
我猜你还没听说？
So I'm guessing you haven't heard?
（笑）到中午这里华氏106度。
[laughs] It's 106 here by noon, man.
我要在凌晨两点前赶第一班。
I'm on the first one by 2 a.m.
我们直到日落才停下来。
We don't stop till sundown.
如果他们在纽约投下炸弹，
If they dropped a bomb on New York City,
我不会知道的。
I would not know about it.
他们没有，但他们刚刚向我们扔了一个。
Well, they didn't, but they just dropped one on us.
约翰·达顿死了。
John Dutton died.
真的吗?发生了什么事?
Really? What happened?
那是另一个故事了。
Well, that's a story for another time.
听着，我需要你的帮助，兄弟。
Listen, I need your help, brother.
是的。我能做什么？
Yeah. What can I do?
你能把我们所有的马移动多快？
How fast can you move all of our horses?
-我们得腾出点现金。-看，伙计，
- We got to free up some cash. - Look, man,
你们这么急着买这些东西，好吗？
you guys rushed into buying these things, all right?
不要急于出售。
Don't rush selling them.
好吧?让我用正确的方式来做。
Okay? Let me do this the right way.
我是说，尽可能快地行动。
Well, I mean, move as fast as you can.
那里卖不掉的，我们就在这里卖。
What we don't sell there we'll disperse at a sale up here.
让我把这里的马都卖了，好吗？
Let me sell all the show horses down here, okay?
他们会把1美元的30美分带到那里。
They're gonna bring 30 cents on the dollar up there.
大便。我们的头在断头台上。
Shit. Our heads are in the guillotine.
是的。我们有麻烦了。
Yeah. We're in a real spot.
好吧，好吧，这不会让事情变得更好
Okay, well, that's not gonna make it any better.
好吧?让我用正确的方式来做，好吗？
All right? Let me do this the right way, okay?
我觉得你儿子不知道。
I don't think your boy knows.
要我把电话递给他吗？
You want me to hand him the phone?
我是说，说实话，兄弟，我…
I mean, to be honest with you, brother, I...
…我不忍心。
...I don't have the heart.
好吧，别担心
All right, don't worry about it.
是的。
Yeah.
我来处理这件事
I'll take care of it.
我很感激。
I appreciate it.
我们得把黄石公园的马都卖了。
We got to sell all the Yellowstone horses.
——好吗?-比如大甩卖？
- Okay? - Like fire sale?
不，我们得试着赚大钱，
No, we got to try and get top dollar,
尽我们所能，好吗？
get-get what we can, all right?
好吧，我会打给你的
All right, well, I'll call
-都是常见的嫌疑人。-对，对。
- all the usual suspects. - Yep, yep.
丹妮卡，帮我个忙。
Danica, do me a favor.
带她。跟我走，吉米。
Take her. Walk with me, Jimmy.
(呼出)
[exhales]
听着，请不要解雇我。
Look, please don't fire me.
别误会我。我…我受够了这破事
Don't get me wrong. I... I'm sick of this shit,
我恨死你了
I hate your fucking guts,
但你是这方面的高手之一。
but you are one of the best at this.
他是最擅长这个的，他是最擅长这个的。
He is one of the best at this, he's one of the best at this.
和…
And...
我想成为这方面的佼佼者。
I want to be one of the best at this.
所以,我……
So, I...
我需要你。
I need you.
好吧，看看这个。终于长出了一些
Well, look at that. Finally growing some huevos.
对你有好处。
Good for you.
我不会炒了你的，吉米。
I ain't gonna fire you, Jimmy.
但我要让你回家一周。
But I'm gonna send you home for the week.
我给你放一周假，好吗？
I'm gonna give you the week off, all right?
所以你去抱抱那个黑发女人。
So you go snuggle that brunette.
等等，你要放我一周假？
Wait, you're giving me the week off?
这是好消息。
That's the good news.
坏消息就是原因。
Bad news is why.
约翰·达顿去世了。
John Dutton passed away.
♪ somber music ♪
♪
Wh……如何?
Wh... How?
我不知道。我不——这有关系吗？
I don't know. I don't-- Does it matter?
现在已经没什么区别了。
It don't make a difference now.
我知道你们很亲密。我很抱歉。花一周的时间。
I know y'all were close. I'm sorry. Take a week.
他是唯一一个
He was the only one that ev--
就这一周吧，吉米。好吧?
Just take the week, Jimmy. Okay?
(咳嗽)
[coughs]
我带他去吧，丹妮卡。
I'll take him, Danica.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
(普通员工)
[grunts]
你在那儿干什么，伙计？
What are you doing there, bud?
周末我去，但这一周我不去了。
I'll take the weekend, but I'm not gonna take the week.
他是一个牛仔。
He was a cowboy.
所以他不想因为他而耽误工作。
So he wouldn't have wanted work missed because of him.
他妈的。对不起。
Fuck. Sorry.
嗯…
Um...
是的。
Yeah.
天啊，我讨厌竞技场的灰尘。我也很难过，你知道吗？
Boy, I hate that old arena dust. Gets to me, too, you know?
吉米，你能做的最好的事就是
Best thing you can do, Jimmy, is just
超过它。
outrun it.
♪
♪ pulsing, dramatic music ♪
♪ somber music ♪
♪
她是在为州政府提供法律建议吗？
[Dillard] Was she providing legal advice for the state?
不,不。
No, no.
那是……(抽泣)
It was a... [sniffles]
严格的私人关系。
a strictly personal relationship.
不是在蒙大拿
Wasn't in Montana
做生意吗?
conducting business?
据我所知没有。
Not that I'm aware of, no.
和你住在一起？
Staying here with you?
是的。
Yeah.
你介意我们帮她收拾东西吗？
Do you mind if we collect her things?
她的衣服吗?
Her clothes?
我猜她有个手提箱。
I'm assuming she had a suitcase.
哦。
Oh.
是的。
Yeah.
嗯，在，在楼上。
Um, it's, um, it's upstairs.
-我去拿。-哦，没关系。
- I'll go get it. - Oh, that's okay.
我们不能让你碰它，
Um, we can't have you touching it,
只要你告诉我们它在哪里。
if you just tell us where it is.
为什么，为什么她的衣服会
Why would, uh, why would her clothing
跟她的袭击有关吗？
be relevant to her attack?
新闻说这是一起劫车案。
The-the news said it was a carjacking.
警官就是这么说的。
That's what the officer said.
警官不是侦探。
Officers aren't detectives.
没有人试图打开车门。
There was no attempt to open the vehicle door.
窗户是关着的。
Uh, window was down.
钱包放在膝上。
Purse in her lap.
看起来更像是她被盯上了。
It appears more like she was targeted.
卧室在楼上吗？
Is the bedroom upstairs?
等等，搜查这栋房子，
Well, wait, to-to search this house,
你得有搜查令才行。
you're gonna have to have a warrant.
我们不需要搜查令。你已经给了我们
We don't need a warrant. You already gave us
允许进入房子。
permission to enter the house.
我可没允许你搜查。
I did not give you permission to search it.
你也没有看到任何可疑的东西
Nor have you witnessed anything suspicious
给你停职的权力
to give you the authority to suspend
搜查令的要求。
the requirement of a warrant.
有人会说你现在的行为很可疑。
One could argue your behavior right now is suspicious.
什么，因为我不想让你翻遍我的房子？
What, 'cause I don't want you rummaging through my house?
我在行使我的权利。
I am exercising my rights.
也许你不记得我是做什么的了，
Maybe you don't recall what I do for a living,
但我他妈是州检察长
but I am the fucking attorney general of the state.
而你却把我当成嫌疑犯。
And you're treating me like I'm a suspect.
不，我没有。
Uh, n-no, I wasn't.
但我现在会的。
But I will now.
好吧，我去。
All right, I'll go.
我上楼去给你拿。
I'll go upstairs and I'll get it for you.
我想我们已经过去了。
I think we're past that.
我们会带着搜查令回来的。
We'll come back with a warrant.
搜查令需要灯光，
Warrant entails lights,
警笛，新闻人员。
sirens, news crews.
你知道的。
You know the deal.
你当然知道。
Course you do.
你他妈是司法部长。
You're the fucking attorney general.
[门开，门关]
[door opens, closes]
♪ suspenseful music ♪
♪
(压缩包)
[unzipping bags]
早....。
Morning.
不知道会有多少。
Don't know how many to expect.
是的。
Yeah.
每年都在减少。
Fewer every year.
谢谢你这么做。
Thank you for doing this.
哦，我喜欢这样做。
Oh, I enjoyed doing it.
烹饪是唯一有意义的工作
Cooking is the only meaningful task
你可以在不到一小时内完成。
you can complete in less than an hour.
我还能想到其他一些。
I can think of a few others.
你想把这些放在餐厅吗？
You want these in the dining room?
不。
No.
我再也不会踏进那个餐厅一步了。
I'm not stepping foot in that dining room ever again.
我们就在这儿吃吧。
Let's eat here.
听起来不错。
Sounds good to me.
泰特吗?
Tate?
你能告诉你爸爸早餐准备好了吗？
Will you tell your father breakfast is ready?
我们就在这里吃。
We're gonna eat in here.
(门)
[door opens]
[泰特]嘿，早餐准备好了。
[Tate] Hey, breakfast is ready.
爸爸?
Dad?
早餐。
Breakfast.
马上就来，伙计。
Be right there, bud.
(铃声播放)
[ringtone playing]
嘿。
Hey.
我刚和你哥哥见过面
[Dillard] I just met with your brother.
你认识这个莎拉·阿特伍德吗？
You know this Sarah Atwood?
我从未见过她，但我知道她。
I never met her but I know of her.
你知道发生什么事了吗？
You know what happened?
劫车,对吧?
Carjacking, right?
不，伙计，她是目标
No, man, she was targeted.
你哥哥拒绝合作。
Your brother is refusing to cooperate.
你感到惊讶吗？
Does that surprise you?
不是真的。
Not really.
是我左手中的文件吗
Is the file in my left hand
跟我右手里的文件有关吗，凯西？
connected to the file in my right hand, Kayce?
我觉得我哥哥和这两份文件有关系吗？
Do I think my brother had anything to do with either file?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我觉得她跟这事有关吗？
Do I think she had something to do with it?
是啊，我觉得这一切都和她有关。
Yeah, I think she had everything to do with it.
你知道她为谁工作吗？
You know who she works for?
纽约律师事务所。
Law firm in New York.
谁是她的客户，迪拉德？
Who's her client, Dillard?
你告诉我。
You tell me.
机场。
The airport.
。
Okay.
那么，司法部长
So, the attorney general
是有性关系吗
was having a sexual relationship
与外部顾问
with outside counsel
关于开发项目
on the development project
. . .
that your father shut down.
你开始明白了吗？
You starting to get the picture?
Kayce ,
Look, Kayce,
手榴弹爆炸的次数够多了
you've had enough grenades go off
在你的世界里，所以如果你需要我们
in your world, so if you need us to
这里加速或减速，
speed up or slow down over here,
because when the lid comes off of this mess...
这个烂摊子已经对我们造成了最大的伤害。
This mess has already hurt us as much as it can.
你踩油门，我的朋友。
You mash on the gas, my friend.
你哥哥在爆炸范围内。
Your brother's in the blast radius.
嗯，他把自己放在那里。
Well, he put himself there.
♬有趣的音乐♬
♪ intriguing music ♪
♪
(电话响了)
[phone rings]
还记得格兰特·霍顿吗？
You remember Grant Horton?
特殊的活动吗?
Special activities?
是的，他在那边
Yeah, he's over there.
你有地址吗？
Do you have an address?
我要去甩掉这混蛋。
I'm gonna go shake this fucker.
好的，我会寄过去的。
Yeah, I'll send it through.
买个新手机和新号码。
Hey, get a new phone and a new number.
你把这个扔进垃圾桶，好吗？
You throw this one in the fucking trash, all right?
完成了。
Done.
(手机铃声)
[phone chimes]
你怎么从来不在家做这样的菜？
Why don't you ever cook like this at home?
-我在家就这么做。——(嘲笑)
- I do cook like this at home. - [scoffs]
一碗麦片没有煮熟。
A bowl of cereal ain't cooking.
现在你只能吃麦片了。
Well, now cereal's what you get.
我要给你看样东西。
I got to show you something.
>神秘音乐
♪ mysterious music ♪
♪
(Beth喘息声)
[Beth gasps]
她是联络人。
She was the point of contact.
我他妈就知道。
I fucking knew it.
警察正在包围杰米。
The police are circling Jamie.
这一切很快就会达到高潮。
This is all gonna come to a head real quick.
哦……
Oh...
如果他们逮捕杰米，
If they arrest Jamie,
他会唱出我们父亲的所有秘密。
he will sing every secret our father ever had.
他会毁了这个家族的名声来挽救自己的。
He will ruin this family's name to save his own.
我们无能为力。
There's not much we can do.
全世界都在关注。
The whole world is watching.
你对此无能为力。
There's not much you can do about it.
最好的谎言有90%是真的，而我他妈是最好的骗子。
The best lies are 90% true, and I'm the best fucking liar.
你把杰米留给我。
You leave Jamie to me.
(模糊聊天)
[indistinct chatter]
♪ pastoral music ♪
♪
(所有的发声)
[all vocalizing]
(手机振动)
[phone vibrates]
是的。
Yeah.
劳埃德，那家伙多大了？
Lloyd, how old is that maneater?
三。
Three.
是的，他三岁了。
He's three-year-old, yeah.
我今天下午就能把他送到那里。
I can have him there by this afternoon.
好吧。
All right.
嘿，Colby，装好
Hey, Colby, load up
把那三岁的孩子送到比林斯家，好吗？
that three-year-old and get him to the Billings, will you?
我告诉你，他不对。别把他放到拍卖会上。
I'm telling you, he ain't right. Don't put him in an auction.
他不会去拍卖的。
He ain't going to the fucking auction.
他要坐车去墨西哥。
He's taking a ride to Mexico.
♬《艰难的生活》作者：克里斯·斯台普顿♬
♪ "Hard Livin'" by Chris Stapleton ♪
♬我以前喜欢找人打架♬
♪ I used to love to look for a fight ♪
>我会喝醉，然后把灯射灭
♪ I'd get drunk and shoot out the lights ♪
♬我被认为是失控的…♪我> < /
♪ I was known to get out of hand... ♪
嘘，嘘，嘘。
Hep, hep, hep.
♬一个粗暴和吵闹的…♪我> < /
♪ A rough and rowdy... ♪
好吧，让我们把妈妈和孩子分开。
All right, let's split the mamas from the babies.
♬从来没有想过♬
♪ Never thought ♪
♬它会发生在我身上…♪我> < /
♪ It would happen to me... ♪
不错的工作。
Nice work.
[牛仔发声，呼喊]
[cowboys vocalizing, exclaiming]
(吹口哨)
[whistling]
♪ Hard living ♪
♬不像以前那么容易了…♪我> < /
♪ Ain't easy as it used to be... ♪
[沃克]见鬼，我们才刚到这里，
[Walker] Hell, we just got here,
现在我们要装货了？
now we're loading 'em?
我知道。
I know.
提特，沃克，该你们了。
Teeter, Walker, you're up.
♬从未想过…♪我> < /
♪ Never thought... ♪
哈！-[提特]哈！
- [Walker] Hyah! - [Teeter] Hyah!
嘿。嘿，嘿，嘿！
Hey. Hey, hey, hey!
[继续发声，呼喊]
[vocalizing, exclaiming continues]
(吹口哨)
[whistling]
♬但这艰难的生活…♪我> < /
♪ But this hard living... ♪
嘘，嘘，嘘。嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
Shh, shh, shh, shh. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
♬不像以前那么容易了♬
♪ Ain't easy as it used to be ♪
[马轻声哀鸣]
[horse whinnying softly]
我应该让你去
I ought to let you
站在那儿渴死吧。
stand there and die of thirst.
(间歇性燃烧)
[chuffing]
♪ suspenseful music ♪
♪
(大声嘶叫着)
[neighs loudly]
[马嘶鸣]
[horse neighs shrilly]
(鼻息,乡下人)
[snorts, chuffs]
(蹄有力)
[hoof clomping]
-[嘶嘶声]-啊！
- [neighs] - Aah!
科尔比卡特。
[Colby] Carter.
♪ tense music ♪
卡特。
Carter.
[卡特]我需要帮助。
[Carter] I need help.
♪
-卡特。-[马蹄声]
- Carter. - [hooves clomping]
(耶)
[neighing]
保持静止。
Stay real still.
好吧。
Okay.
当我把他推回去时
When I push him back,
你尽可能快地爬出来。
you crawl out as fast as you can.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
走了。
Go.
(萧萧)
[neighs]
(普通员工)
[grunts]
[马大声嘶鸣]
[horse neighing loudly]
[远距离射击]
[gunshot in distance]
伊森，和兽群待在一起。劳埃德!
Ethan, stay with the herd. Lloyd!
这是……是我的错。他……
It's... it's my fault. He...
他告诉我不要一个人去隔间，
He told me not to go in a stall alone,
但是他把水洒了。我…他的立场让我失望。
but he spilled his water. I... His side got me down.
>悲伤的音乐
♪ mournful music ♪
♪
这是我的错。
This is my fault.
都是我的错。
It's-it's my fault.
这不是你的错。
It ain't your fault.
如果是谁的错，那就是我的错。
If it's anyone's fault, it's mine.
(线响)
[line ringing]
嘿,嘿!嘿,嘿!
Hey, hey! Hey, hey!
[沃克]嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿，嘿。
[Walker] Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
[提特]嘿，嘿。嘿。
[Teeter] Hey, hey. Hey.
(铃声播放)
[ringtone playing]
嘿。是的，他们都装好了。
Hey. Yeah, they're loaded up.
卡车正在撤离。
Trucks are pulling out right now.
我应该拿最后一个
I should have the last one
一小时后就上路了。
on the road in about an hour.
嗯?
Huh?
好的，先生，我现在就告诉她。
Yes, sir, I'll tell her right now.
一切都好吗？
Everything all right?
(抽泣)
[sniffles]
我刚失去了我最好的朋友杰
Just lost my best friend, Jay.
>悲伤的音乐
♪ mournful music ♪
♪
-♬ -[对话听不清]
- ♪ - [dialogue inaudible]
一切都还好吗？
Is everything okay?
什么都不好，伊森。
Nothing's okay, Ethan.
不再......。
Not anymore.
帮我一下。
Give me a hand.
是的。
Yeah.
♪
提特，我能帮你吗？
Teeter, can I give you a hand?
我可没忘记怎么把马卸下来。
I ain't forgot how to unsaddle a fucking horse.
♪
[杰克]里普，说发生什么事了？
[Jake] Rip say what happened?
一头种马把卡特撞倒了。
A stud got Carter down.
科尔比进去帮忙时踢了他一脚。
Kicked Colby when he went in to help.
很快。
It was quick.
没想到会来。
Never saw coming.
好像那有什么区别似的。
Like that makes a difference.
只是说他没有受苦。
Just saying he didn't suffer.
他是一个牛仔。
He's a cowboy.
受苦就是工作。
Suffering's the job.
我只希望他能多受点苦
I just wish he would have suffered a little longer
这样我就能说再见了
so I could say goodbye.
♪ plaintive music ♪
♪
♪ somber music ♪
(电机空转)
[motor idling]
我们从这里走回去。
We'll walk back from here.
我们要把他埋在这里？
We gonna bury him here?
我肯定他想和家人在一起。
I'm sure he'd like to be close to his family.
我肯定他们想让他待在身边，这样他们就可以去看他了。
I'm sure they'd like to have him close so they can visit.
我是说爷爷。
I meant Grandpa.
是的。是的，我们把他埋在这里。
Yeah. Yeah, we'll bury him here.
在哪里?
Where?
在我妈妈旁边。
Next to my mother.
你想葬在这里吗？
This where you want to be buried?
这是……那得由你来决定。
That's... that's for you to decide.
好吧，如果你想要的话。
Well, if it's what you want.
嗯，我只是…
Well, I just...
我只是想靠近你。
I just want to be close to you.
我会在家的。
I'll be at home.
除非这是我们的家。
Unless this is our home.
不，这里不是我们的家。
No, here's not our home.
不再......。
Not anymore.
告诉你妈妈我马上就上来，好吗？
Tell your mother I'll be up in a minute, okay?
嘿。
Hey.
我不想埋葬你。
I don't want to bury you.
任何地方。
Anywhere.
我当然希望你能，孩子
I sure hope you do, son,
因为我无法活下去
because I couldn't survive the alternative.
凯德嘿。
[Cade] Hey.
我现在看到了。我知道该怎么做。
I can see it now. I know what to do.
好。
Good.
我需要你的帮助。
I need your help.
You have it.
这是有风险的。
Comes with a risk.
所有的恩惠都是如此，凯西
All favors do, Kayce.
♪
(微波炉声)
[microwave beeps]
(门关闭)
[door closes]
哪个铺位是他的？
Which bunk is his?
我示范给你看。
I'll show you.
不急着清理。
No rush to clear it out.
我和他妈妈谈过了。她喜欢他的东西。
I spoke with his mother. She'd like his things.
见鬼，他也没什么
Well, hell, he ain't got much--
谷仓里的马鞍
a saddle in the barn
还有这个储物柜。
and this foot locker.
(叹息)
[sighs]
等等，这不是不吉利吗？
Wait, isn't that bad luck?
是的，直到你的运气用完。
Well, it is until your luck runs out.
那就找对地方了。
Then it's the right spot.
如果你不介意，
If you don't mind,
也许你可以把它留下。
maybe you could leave that.
他有一位女士要回来。
He's got a lady coming back.
她需要一些东西来支撑。
She's gonna need something to cling to.
很好。
Fair enough.
哦……
Oh...
你给我一个地址
You give me an address,
我明天早上第一件事就是把这个柜子寄出去。
I'll mail this locker first thing in the morning.
就在盒子上。
It's right here on the box.
好吧。
Okay.
小卡特在这里？
Little Carter in here?
我没见过他。
I haven't seen him.
谢谢你，劳埃德。
Thank you, Lloyd.
你不要浪费时间。
You don't waste any time.
这可不是你想要的东西。
It ain't the kind of thing you want laying around.
你把它埋在哪了？
Where'd you bury it?
我们没有掩埋它。
We didn't bury it.
那个人喂狼。
That one feeds the wolves.
没有卡特?
No Carter?
策略的房间。
Tack room.
谢谢。
Thanks.
(敲门)
[knocking]
(门关闭)
[door closes]
我在这个房间里坠入爱河。
I fell in love in this room.
我在这个房间里怀孕了。
I got pregnant in this room.
然后我告诉我一生的挚爱…
And then I told the love of my life...
…我再也不想见到他了
...that I never wanted to see him again.
他就坐在你现在的位置。
He was sat right where you are.
你为什么这么做？
Why'd you do that?
(叹息)
[sighs]
我感到羞愧。
I was ashamed.
我很害怕。
And I was scared.
你把这些都发泄在你最爱的人身上，
You take these things out on the ones you love the most,
出于某种原因。
for some reason.
(叹息)
[sighs]
你在自责，是吧？
You're blaming yourself, huh?
还能怪谁呢？
Who else is there to blame?
根本不应该责怪任何人。
There is no one to blame at all.
我不应该一个人在里面的。
I wasn't supposed to be in there by myself.
好吧，这就是你的理由。
Well, that is your reason.
里普的理由就是这个
Rip's reason will be that
他应该早点把那匹马卖掉
he should have sold that horse sooner
或者他应该回来的。
or he should have come back in.
劳埃德在自责，原因我也想不出来。
Lloyd is blaming himself for a reason that I can't think of.
但事实是，亲爱的……
But the reality is, honey...
…Colby做了一个选择。
...Colby made a choice.
他看到你有麻烦了。
He saw you in trouble.
他选择了帮助你。
And he chose to help you.
我很高兴他这么做了。
And I'm sure glad that he did.
我很感激。
I'm grateful.
你也应该这样。
And you should be, too.
否则，他就白干了。
Otherwise, he did it for nothing.
所以，你可以尊重他的牺牲。
So, you can honor his sacrifice.
或者你可以浪费它。
Or you can squander it.
那将是你的错。
And that will be your fault.
(叹息)
[sighs]
你今晚要待在这里吗？
You gonna stay here tonight?
我不知道。
I-I don't know.
如果我是你，我，
Well, if I were you, I, uh,
我可不想一个人面对这一切。
I wouldn't want to wrestle with this by myself.
我想和家人在一起。
I'd want to be with my family.
我没有家庭。
I don't got a family.
你当然知道。
Sure you do.
(门)
[door opens]
(门关闭)
[door closes]
>宁静的音乐
♪ serene music ♪
♪
【脚步声】
[footsteps approaching]
我要生个火。
I'm gonna light a fire.
太热了，不能生火。
It's too warm for a fire.
我知道。
I know.
但我喜欢看他们。
But I like looking at 'em.
一个小…
A little...
童子军果汁。
Boy Scout juice.
瞧。
Et voilá.
现在，当你扔威士忌酒杯的时候
Now, when you throw your whiskey glass
在火中，你会得到一个大火球。
in the fire, you get a big fireball.
你会觉得自己做了什么。
You'll really feel like you did something.
我为什么要把杯子扔进火里，贝丝？
Why would I throw my glass in the fire, Beth?
宝贝，你得扔点东西。
Well, baby, you need to throw something.
嘿，我不会看着你的
Hey, I'm not gonna watch you
整晚都把它装在瓶子里。
bottle this up all night.
(液体浇注)
[liquid pouring]
你想让我扔东西吗？
You want me to throw something?
感觉不错吧？
Feel good, huh?
你知道，当我发现自己站在治疗师的立场上…
You know, when I find myself in the position of therapist...
…这个家糟透了。
...this family's pretty fucked.
那么，你需要什么？
So, what do you need?
你需要什么来……
What do you need to...
…不再感到痛苦和内疚，
...not feel this pain or this guilt,
不管你是什么感觉？
whatever it is you're feeling?
我只需要时间和你，贝丝。
All I ever need is time and you, Beth.
>希望的音乐
♪ hopeful music ♪
♪
如果我开始感到内疚
You know, if I started feeling guilty
对于所有的…我所犯的错误……
for all the... the mistakes I've made...
…我只会感到内疚。
...guilt is all I'd feel.
我希望我自己去吗？
Do I wish I would have gone myself?
当然，我喜欢，但是……
Hell yeah, I do, but...
该死的，我没有。
goddamn it, I didn't.
这是一份危险的工作。
It's a dangerous job.
总有一天它也会杀了我。
And one day it'll kill me, too.
你知道，这个房间…
You know, this room...
…她是这所房子里我唯一喜欢的人。
...is the only one in the house I like.
是的。
Yeah.
我也是。
Me too.
你能给我解释一下吗？
You care to explain this to me?
我没有。
I do not.
我这样做对牧场不利。
What I'm doing isn't best for the ranch.
这是对你最好的选择。
It's what's best for you.
对我们来说。
For us.
我明天晚上回来。
I'll be back tomorrow night.
承诺吗?
Promise?
我发誓。
I swear.
♪ pensive music ♪
♪
我现在看到了。
I can see it now.
我知道该怎么做。
I know what to do.
相信我。
Believe in me.
(轻声嘲笑)
[scoffs softly]
我一直相信你，凯西。
I've always believed in you, Kayce.
我爱你。
I love you.
回到我们身边。
Come back to us.
我向你保证。
You have my word.
[微风轻吹]
[wind softly whistling]
早....。
Morning.
(贝丝叹息)
[Beth sighs]
没错。
That it is.
我是说，早上好。
I mean, good morning.
好吧，这是相当冒昧的
Well, that's fairly presumptuous
根据我们最近连续几个早上的记录。
based on the string of mornings we've put together lately.
你想吃早餐吗？
You want breakfast?
已经做好了。
Already made it.
你能让凯西等他结束后和我一起去门廊吗？
Um, can you ask Kayce to join me on the porch when he's done?
他离开了。
He left.
离开哪里?
Left where?
(吹口哨吹)
[whistle blows]
[父母欢呼，吵嚷]
[parents cheering, clamoring]
来吧，艾丽。别让他们出去。
Come on, Ally. Don't let 'em out.
哦，递给我！通过了!
Oh, pass it! Pass left!
开枪吧!
Shoot it!
-[吹口哨]-[呜呜声]
- [whistle blows] - [whoops]
这就对了！干得好，女士们。
There you go! Nice job, ladies.
[欢呼，掌声继续]
[cheering, applause continuing]
好工作!干得好！
Good job! Way to go!
干得好，运动健将。
Good job, sport.
好吧，你做得对。
All right, you did the right thing.
当有人站在你面前时，
When someone's posted up in front of you,
你把球传给空位前锋。
you pass to the open forward.
但她实现了目标。
But she got the goal.
是啊，但你赢了。
Yeah, but you got the win.
来吧。
Come on.
安全带。
Seat belt.
♬不祥的音乐♬
♪ ominous music ♪
♪
开车。
Drive.
发动汽车，开车
Start the car and drive
或者你可以收拾残局。
or you can clean up the mess.
我要去哪里？
Where am I going?
直行，开到他妈限速就行。
Just drive straight and drive the fucking speed limit.
你应该感到害怕。
You should be scared.
你知道你爸爸是做什么的吗？
You know what your daddy does for a living?
你知道我是谁吗？
Do you know who I am?
我没有。
I do not.
在私营部门太自负了，你忘了
Get so cocky in the private sector you forgot
在目标身上建立直系亲属关系，格兰特？
to build out immediate family on a target, Grant?
这不是你被训练的方式。
It's not the way you were trained.
听着，伙计，我们所做的，是严格的
Listen, man, what we do, it is strictly--
我要你听我说。我不想让你说话。
I want you to listen. I don't want you to talk.
我就是你。
I am what you are.
你明白我的意思吗？
You understand what I mean by that?
是的，我明白你的意思。
Yeah, I understand what you mean.
你得到了分离。你不能被连接。
You got separation. You can't be connected.
太好了，你省去了我的麻烦。
Great, you saved me the trouble.
但如果你想对冲你的赌注
But if you try to hedge your bets
和家人保持距离，
by getting distance with my family,
我会把你的画在墙上。
I will paint yours on the fucking wall.
我应该当着她的面杀了你
I should kill you in front of her
因为你对我父亲的所作所为，
for what you did to my father,
但我愿意用我的家人换你的
but I'm gonna trade my family for yours.
你以为别人不会碰你吗？
You think you can't be touched?
看看这对我来说有多容易。
Look how easy this was for me.
我在球队里待了12年。
I have 12 years in the teams.
想想我有多少朋友。
Think about how many friends I have.
你不会想吵架的。你赢不了的。
You don't want this fight. You can't win it.
我们有足够的距离。
We got enough separation.
-我们不需要别的东西了。-靠边停车
- We don't need anything else. - Pull over.
我有你的国防部档案。
I have your DoD file.
我知道你的地址。
I know your address.
我知道你父母住哪
I know where your parents live,
我知道你妻子在哪里工作，我什么都知道。
I know where your wife works, I know everything.
你碰了我，但我可以随时碰你。
You touched me, but I can touch you whenever I want.
它被困住了。你和我，我们很好。
It's bottled up. You and me, we're good.
我们还差得远，你都看不出来
We're so far from fucking good you couldn't see it
站在西榆树街2713号的屋顶上
standing on your roof at 2713 West Elm.
如果我是你，我就搬家。
If I were you, I'd move.
因为我可能明天醒来再做决定
'Cause I might wake up tomorrow and decide
我们没有交易。明白了吗？
we don't have a deal. You got me?
不!
No!
请停止。
Stop, please.
在我的家乡，我们称之为计数政变。
Where I come from, we call that counting coup.
也就是说我带走了你的一部分灵魂
That means I took a piece of your soul
我要留着它
and I'm gonna keep it.
是的，你应该哭。
And, yeah, you should cry.
好好跟你老婆解释吧。
Have fun explaining this to your wife.
我出来后，你就走。
When I get out, you take off.
你再回头，我就杀了你俩。
You look back, I kill you both.
♪
怎么样？
How'd it go?
我想他能理解。
I think he understands.
你算政变了吗？
Did you count coup?
我数了一下政变。
I counted coup.
然后他明白了。
Then he understands.
♪ dramatic music ♪
♪